And what I want is that so I say hell no we don't need to say hello over here but as you see
there's an image of aliens walking in Paris with the I fell tower I fell tower in the background
and another image of me in a suit so what I want you to do is that first I want you
to let's say we want to remove this light over here right this lamp over here so I want you to
remove the tall lamp in the left of the aliens image background and I want you to eliminate it
as it's never even existed and then I want you to add me so let's say I want you to generate
a full height version of me and put it in the background of aliens photos
walking
where let's say where the blank coat guy is going and make me
walking in the direction of the camera or let's say make me walking towards the camera right